{
    "subject": "resource/Paul_Stephenson_(police_officer)",
    "predicate": "property/honorificSuffix",
    "object": "resource/Queen's_Police_Medal",
    "human_readable": "Paul Stephenson (police officer) holds the Queen's Police Medal.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8631365299224854,
            "question": "What is the name of the award that Paul Stephenson holds?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8408686518669128,
            "question": "Who awards the Queen's Police Medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.817968487739563,
            "question": "What type of medal is the Queen's Police Medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8013640642166138,
            "question": "What award has Paul Stephenson received?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7476929426193237,
            "question": "Who is Paul Stephenson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7272167205810547,
            "question": "Is Paul Stephenson a member of the police force?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7249215841293335,
            "question": "What does the Queen's Police Medal recognize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6845048069953918,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the Queen's Police Medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5542029738426208,
            "question": "What profession does Paul Stephenson have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42215558886528015,
            "question": "What is special about Paul Stephenson's achievement?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paul Stephenson (police officer) holds the Queen's Police Medal.",
            "html": "dbpedia_544_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What profession does Paul Stephenson have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_544_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the Queen's Police Medal?",
            "html": "dbpedia_544_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does the Queen's Police Medal recognize?",
            "html": "dbpedia_544_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_544_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_544_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_544_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_544_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_544_145.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_544_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_544_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_544_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_544_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_544_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this response is that while Sir Paul Stephenson QPM is indeed mentioned in the documents, there is no information provided to confirm that he holds the Queen's Police Medal. The document mentions that he was awarded the Queen's Policing Medal in May 2000 and a knighthood in June 2008, but it does not explicitly state that he holds the Queen's Police Medal."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents support that Sir Paul Stephenson holds the Queen's Police Medal, as explicitly mentioned in one of the provided texts."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Paul Stephenson (police officer) was awarded the Queen's Police Medal for services to policing in May 2000, which contradicts the statement that it is incorrect.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}